Finding Aid for the National Association of Composers, U.S.A. records PASC-M.0080
UCLA Library Special Collections
National Association of Composers, U.S.A. records
1933-1988
UCLA Library Special Collections
National Association of Composers, U.S.A.
PASC-M.0080
9 Linear Feet (6 document boxes, 14 flat boxes, and 1 oversize flat box)
This collection contains the records of the National Association of Composers, USA (NACUSA) and those of its preceding body, the National Association of American Composers and Conductors (NAACC). Records include minutes, correspondence, treasurer's reports, chapter information, concert programs and announcements, clippings, and other material; and cover the transition from the NAACC to NACUSA. Also included are musical scores contributed by approximately 110 of its member composers.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Audio materials in this collection are restricted and require production of listening copies. To access materials, notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9924703293606533
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of California State University, Dominguez Hills, 1988.
Biography/History
The National Association of American Composers and Conductors (NAACC) was a non-profit and volunteer- run organization founded in 1933, in New York, by Henry K. Hadley. The NAACC was one of the longest standing organizations in the United States devoted to the promotion and performance of American concert hall music. The organization maintained chapters in Los Angeles, Philadelphia, Colorado, Indiana, and the District of Columbia, and included its members in annual concerts, given to the public free of charge. The NAACC was led by Henry Hadley until his death in 1937, after which his wife, Inez Barbour Hadley, took over and ran the association until her death in 1971. After a period of inactivity, UCLA professor and conductor John Vincent took on the leadership of the NAACC in 1975 and changed the association's name to National Association of Composers, USA (NACUSA) and moved the headquarters from New York City to Los Angeles. By 2015, NACUSA was presenting several chamber concerts each year featuring music by its members, publishing a newsletter, and holding a national contest for young composers aged 18-30. Over the course of its existence, the organization has included many well-known American composers as members.
Source: National Association of American Composers and Conductors Papers, JPB 03-15
Scope and Content
This collection contains the records of the National Association of Composers, USA (NACUSA) and those of its preceding body, the National Association of American Composers and Conductors (NAACC). Records include meeting minutes, financial reports, chapter records, newsletters, correspondence, concert programs and calendars, competition and other event announcements, clippings, scrapbooks, and notes belonging to its recording secretary. A large part of the collection contains musical scores by approximately 110 member composers, submitted for performances and competitions, and collected by the organization.
Organization and Arrangement
The collection has been arranged in the following series:
Series 1. Scores
Subseries 1.1. Numbered scores
Subseries 1.2. Unnumbered scores
Series 2. Organizational records.
Related Material
John Vincent Collection (Collection PASC-M 31). Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, UCLA.
National Association of American Composers and Conductors Papers, JPB 03-15. Music Division, The New York Public Library for the Performing Arts.
NACUSA online archive: http://www.music-usa.org/nacusa/
Vocal music -- Scores.; Instrumental music -- Scores.; Music -- Societies, etc.; Scores.; Vincent, John; National Association for American Composers and Conductors
- Series 1. Scores, 1950-1986
  Scope and Content
  This series contains scores that were submitted to NAACC/ NACUSA by member composers for inclusion in various competitions and performances. Unnumbered scores have been separated from scores that were numbered by the organization, presumably as an attempt to archive them. No index exists for these numbered scores. There is overlap in composers between numbered and unnumbered scores.
  - Subseries 1.1. Numbered scores, 1968-1983
    - 1. Cotton, Jeffrey V.: Dream Within a Dream. For soprano, flute, cello and piano, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - 2. Molineux, Allen: Moon Eclipse Exorcism (male vocal solo with piano accompaniment), undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - 3. Molineux, Allen: Free Fancy. For solo flute, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - 4. Tautenhahn, Gunther: Of Dreams and Nightmares. For 11 instruments, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - 5. Tautenhahn, Gunther: Numeric Serenade. For piano and orchestra, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - 6. Tautenhahn, Gunther: Woodwind Quartet. For flute, oboe, clarinet, French horn, and bassoon, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - 7. Tautenhahn, Gunther: Pyramid Four. For orchestra, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - 8. Tautenhahn, Gunther: Dialogues/Bowless Violin, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - 9. Tautenhahn, Gunther: Saxophone Quartet. For soprano, alto, tenor and baritone saxophone, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - 10. Tautenhahn, Gunther: Five Bagatelles for String Quartet. For violin I, violin II, viola and cello, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - 11. Tautenhahn, Gunther: Dialogues. For bowless violin and piano, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - 12. Tautenhahn, Gunther: Song of the Midnight Sun. For flute, violin, viola, and cello, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - 13. Tautenhahn, Gunther: Greeley Variations. For violin and bassoon, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - 14. Griffin, Thomas: Prelude and Scherzo. For two pianos, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - 15. Halpin, Brooke:Serenata. For unaccompanied cello, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - 16. Heifitz, Robin: Chirp for Euphonium and Piano, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - 17. Drogin, Barry: Animal Story. For piano, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - 18. Heifitz, Robin: Leviathan for piano, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - 19. Snow, David: Reflections. For mezzo-soprano, horn and piano, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - 20. Simone, Edgardo: Seiche. Violin and cello duet with piano accompaniment, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - 21. Shelton, Margaret Meier: Dialogues for Flute and Piano, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - 22. Kanach, Sharon: "Patterns". Pour quatuor de flutes a bec. Recorder quartet., 1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - 23. Morgan, John: Unknown. For oboe, Bb clarinet, Eb alto sax, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - 24. Heifitz, Robin: Child of the Water. For piano, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - 25. Snow, David: Sonatina for Trumpet and Piano, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - 26. Kowalski, David: Tri-Tetra-Hexa (Dissolutions I). For flute, percussion and violin, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - 27. Kowalski, David: Quintetino. For 2 violins, viola, violincello, and piano, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - 28. Ortiz, William: Quinteto para Metales. For 2 trumpets in Bb, trompa in F, trombone(tenor) and tuba, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - 29. Ortiz, William: Rumba para violonchelo y piano, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - 30. Wager, Gregg: Drop a Tear In This Slot. Words by O. Henry. Vocal solo with piano accompaniment, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - 31. Wager, Gregg: Soul of Chocolate. For Bb clarinet - soprano solo, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - 32. Sanchez, Enrique: I, Bertolt Brecht. Song for tenor and piano, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - 33. Coban, Vincentiu-Cristian: Ethos I. For woodwind quintet., 1981 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - 34. Wager, Gregg: 10 Short Pieces for Piano Solo, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - 35. Andrews, George: Four Bagatelles (Not To Be Trifled With), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - 36. Mohr, Ralph W.: Regina, the Greatest of These. Soprano solo, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - 37. Bulow, Harry: Inventions for Flute and Piano, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - 38. Snow, David: Trio. For alto flute, contrabass, and piano, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - 39. Kanach, Sharon: Directions: N.S. Piano solo, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - 40. Lennon, John: Distances Within Me. For alto saxophone and piano. Commissioned by James Forger, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - 41. Brief, Todd: Concert Etude. For piano, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - 42. Billet, Kirk Evan: Evolution of a Tone Row. For Brass Quartet. 1st trumpet, 2nd trumpet, horn in F, trombone, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - 43. Billet, Kirk Evan: Reflections of Enchantment. Duet for flute and piano, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - 44. Lindsey, David: Transitional Structure I. For solo violin, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - 45. Lindsey, David C.: Reconstructed Prophecies II. For flute, violin, cello and piano, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - 46. Riccardi, Riccardo: Sovrattempo. For flute, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - 47. Riccardi, Riccardo: Quartetto. For flute, oboe, clarinet and bassoon, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - 48. Brief, Todd: Moments. For harp, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - 49. Williams, Michael: Notturno. Piano solo, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - 50. Williams, Michael: Open Music. For woodwind quintet, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - 51. Coban, Vincentiu-Cristian: Metabole I. For clarinet and percussion., undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - 52. Ehle, Robert: The City is Beautiful and Beloved of God. For quartet or choir, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - 53. Ehle, Robert: Lamentations. Four part vocal music, udated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - 54. Ehle, Robert: What Profit Hath He. Four part vocal music, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - 55. Ehle, Robert: Our Life is Short and Tedious. Four part vocal music, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - 56. Ehle, Robert: Bay Psalms-1640. Four part vocal music (with piano part), 1978 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - 57. Richardson, Dana: Amerigo Amphion (Fantacycle for Piano Solo). Piano solo, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - 58. Unknown: Piano Percussion Piece, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - 59. Drozin, Garth M.: Extensities. Sonata for solo contrabass, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - 60. Ortiz- Alvarado, William: Dualidad (For 2 Guitars), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - 61. McGee, Cindy: Wind Quintet No.1. For flute, oboe, clarinet in Bb, Horn in F, and bassoon, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - 62. Runyon, Michael: Variations for Contrabass, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - 63. Runyon, Michael K.: Six Dispositions of Christopher Michael. A song cycle for soprano and piano, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - 64. Drozin, Garth M.: The Unseen Soldier. For snare drum, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - 65. Ehle, Robert: City Etudes - Op.9. For piano, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - 66. Ehle, Robert: Quintet for Brass, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - 68. Ehle, Robert: Piano Etudes for Composer, Op.33., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - 69. Ehle, Robert: Aria for trumpet and piano (Op.11, no.2). For trumpet in C with piano accompaniment, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - 70. Ehle, Robert: Three Hand Study Op.7, No.3. For piano, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - 71. Drozin, Garth M.: Solemn Platitudes. For solo pianoforte, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - 72. Macaulay, Janice: O Lord, You Have Searched and Known Me. For mixed voices, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - 73. Macaulay, Janice: Three Chorale Preludes for Passion Week. For trumpet, reeds and oboe, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - 74. Macaulay, Janice: Sonata for Trumpet. For trumpet and organ, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - 75. Karpman, Laura: Six Forms for Five Brass, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - 76. Karpman, L. A.: Peintures. For flute, bassoon, violin and violin cello, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - 77. Macaulay, Janice: Five Movements for String Quartet, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - 78. Merkin, Robin: Suite of Five Preludes. For solo piano, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - 79. Merkin, Robin: The Bazaar. For flute, oboe, Bb clarinet, bassoon and horn, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - 80. Merkin, Robin: Sonata for Bb Clarinet, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - 81. Ehle, Robert: Suite for Violin Op.41. For unaccompanied violin, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - 82. Ehle, Robert: City is Beautiful and Beloved of God. A contata for soprano, alto, tenor and bass, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - 83. Ehle, Robert: Chorus with Solo: Lamentations, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - 84. Ehle, Robert: Bay Psalms-1640. Choral arrangement., 1978; 9 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - 85. Preobrajenska, Vera N.: American Tone Poem. For symphonic orchestra in three movements, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - 86. Drozin, Garth M.: Extensities. A sonata for solo contrabass, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - 87. Drozin, Garth M.: Of Skin and Metal, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - 88. Drozin, Garth M.: Solemn Platitudes. For solo pianoforte, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - 89. Drozin, Garth M.: The Unseen Soldier. For single snaredrum, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - 90. Ehle, Robert: Sonata for Synthesizer and Piano. "Lost Birds", 1978 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - 91. McGee, Cindy: Piano Percussion Piece. For piano, marimba, vibraphone., 1981 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - 92. McGee, Cindy: King Lear Fragments. For baritone, bass flute, and percussion, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - 93. Kanach, Sharon: Anlage. For flute, violin and cello, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - 94. Saragoza, Justin: Symphony No.4. For chamber orchestra, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - 95. Saragoza, Justin: Network. For pianoforte, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - 96. Saragoza, Justin: Windo Visions. For piano, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - 97. Saragoza, Justin: Formidable to Tyrants Only. Vocal selection, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - 98. Saragoza, Justin: The Prisoner. For piano. Derived from Symphony No.5, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - 99. Saragoza, Justin: Meta Music No.2,3,4 & 5. For electronic synthesizer and tape, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - 100. Saragoza, Justin: Song No. 2. For string quartet, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - 101. Saragoza, Justin: Song No. 3. For string quartet, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - 102. Saragoza, Justin: Heart Drops from the Great Space. For violin, piano, and cello, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - 103. Saragoza, Justin: Meta Music No.1. For piano, cello and violin, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - 104. Saragoza, Justin: Mountain Air (A Ballad). For 3 violins, guitar & vibes, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - 105. Saragoza, Justin: Let 'em Eat Cheese. For violin, oboe, and flute & viola, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - 106. Saragoza, Justin: Debate for Two Pianos (Part 1-A), 1981 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 107. Saragoza, Justin: Theater Piece No.4 (In One Act). Work No.33, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 108. Saragoza, Justin: Nighthawks at Dusk. For piano and orchestra. Song No.11, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 109. Saragoza, Justin: Theatre Piece No.6. For musicians and a poet. Work no.38, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 110. Saragoza, Justin: Theatre Piece No.1. Work No.25, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 111. Saragoza, Justin: Feudal Systems Circa 1980, or, Living in Nevada. For fortepiano and violin, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - 112. Saragoza, Justin: Improvisation No.2 (Work No.32). For acoustic steel string guitar, grand piano and orchestra, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - 113. Saragoza, Justin: 5 Improvisations for String Quartet. Work No.33, no.3, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - 114. Saragoza, Justin: Book of Changes. For piano, cello and violin, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - 115. Nightingale, Barbara: Partita for Accordion, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - 116. Porter, Charles:Three Two-Part Inventions for Double-Reeds. For oboe and bassoon, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - 117. Samuel, Richard: String Quartet, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - 118. Garcia, Orlando J.: Crystalline Sounds of the Night. For solo cello, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - 119. Garcia, Orlando J,: Otanen, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - 120. Garcia, Orlando J.: In This Darkness. Based on a native Peruvian-Indian poem, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - 121. Smith, Dwayne E.: Lady Myrddin's Lament. For solo flute (must have low B natural key), 1983 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - 122. Malinowski, Stephen: Upon the Nipples of Julia's Breast. Text by Robert Herrick. For flute, tenor and harpsichord, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - 123. Malinowski, Stephen: Upon a Delaying Lady. Text by Robert Herrick. For flute, tenor and keyboard, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - 124. Malinowski, Stephen: Upon Jack and Jill. Text by Robert Herrick. For flute, tenor and keyboard, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - 125. Malinowski, Stephen: Lips Tonguelesse. For flute, tenor and keyboard, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - 126. Malinowski, Stephen: Fantasy in F. Piano solo, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - 127. Riccardi, Riccardo: Quartetto. For flute, oboe, clarinet and bassoon, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - 128. Maderich, Robert J., II.: Sonata for Cello and Harp, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - 129. Maderich, Robert J., II.: Whiskers for Flute, Oboe, and Bassoon, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - 130. Van Olese, Philip: Destructions No.1 for Large Metal Building, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - 131. Le Baron, Anne: Dammit to Hell. For bassoon, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 132. Kaiser, Tyler: Cosmopolitan Ethics. For violin, viola, and cello, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 133. Grossman, Deena: Music of Spaces. Trio for violin, Bb clarinet and piano, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 134. Dinesca, Violeta: Atreju. For flute and guitar, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 135. Dinesca, Violeta: Dialogo. For flute and viola, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 136. Dinesca, Violeta: Arabesks. For flute and percussion, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - 137. Brickman, Scott: String Trio. For violin, viola and violin cello, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - 138. Haney, David: Theme and Variations for Piano, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 1.2. Unnumbered scores, 1950-1986
    - Adair, James: Sonata. For harpsichord and violin, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Berlin, David: Essences. For viola and tape, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Berlin, David N.: Interactions. For flute and tape, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Berlin, David: Quintet. For bassoon and strings, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Berlin, David: Quintet. For Woodwinds, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Berlin, David: Synergism #1, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Berlin, David N.: Variants, for orchestra, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bernstein, Steven R.: Against Blame of Women. Words by Gerald, Earl of Desmond, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bestor, Charles: Second Moon of Venus, The. For piano and cassette, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bestor, Charles: Sonata, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bestor, Charles: Suite. For alto saxophone and percussion. 3 copies, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bestor, Charles: Suite for winds. From music written for the play "J.B."., 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bestor, Charles: Three Portraits, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Biggs, John: Scherzo. For the Westwood Wind Quartet, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Biggs, John: Studies in Texture, 1984; 31 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Billet, Kirk Evan: Cantata. Biblical tests for unaccompanied chorus., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bliss, Marilyn: Chameleon. For flute, violoncello and piano, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bliss, Marilyn: Fantasies. For piano solo, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Blyton, Carey: Blue Christmas (A Carol in the Blues Idiom). Words by Peter Westmore, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Blyton, Carey: A Child Was Born, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Blyton, Carey: Lullaby, A. Chrismas carol, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Blyton, Carey: Mistletoe Bough: a Traditional Carol, Op. 61. For SSATBB and piano woodwork, 1971-1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Blyton, Carey: Mixed Bag. Words by Enid Blyton, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Blyton, Carey: Pantomime: Three Easy Pieces. For piano and cello, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Blyton, Carey: Poetry of Dress: Three Songs. For tenor voice and piano. Words by Robert Herrick, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Blyton, Carey: Scherzo. For Bb clarinet and piano, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Blyton, Carey: Seven Polyphonic Amens. For unaccompanied voices, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Blyton, Carey: The Silly Flea (two versions: SATB, counter-tenor and 2 tenors, 2 basses), 1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Blyton, Carey: Six Regional Canadian Folk Songs, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Blyton, Carrey: Stephen Was a Stable- Boy, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Blyton, Carey: Symphony in Yellow. For high voice and harp (or piano). Words by Oscar Wilde, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Blyton, Carey: Woman's World, A. Three songs for female voices with optional piano, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Bradshaw, Merrill: Moments, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Brings, Allen: Madrigali Concertati, The. For soprano, harpsichord and violoncello, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Brockman, Jane E.: Sonata. For clarinet and piano, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Brown, Earle: Folio and 4 Systems, 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Bulow, Harry: Densities. For string quartet, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Butler, Rod: Sunscape. For flute and tape, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Butler, Rod: Variations on Raga Yaman-Kalyan (Dhamar-Tal). For four saxophones, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Campanelli, Richard: Seven Preludes. For piano solos, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Campanelli, Richard: Silence of Alcuin, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Includes 1 reel of 1/4 inch audio tape.
      RESTRICTED ACCESS: Use of audio material requires production of listening copies.
    - Carroll, Nancy: Lazarus. For mixed choir with optional keyboard accompaniment. Text by Jose Asuncion Silva, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Carroll, Nancy: Prayer 30. Canonical Prayerbook of the Mandaens, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Coban, Vincentiu-Cristian: Rise. For percussion solo, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Coyner, Lou: Tycho. For piano and tape, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Crain, Samuel: Flotation Music. For flute and guitar, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Crain, Samuel: Tonescope. For flute, oboe, clarinet and bassoon, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Davidson, Tina: Alternances for Wind Quartet, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Davidson, Tina: Unicorn/Tapestry. For soprano, cello and pre-recorded cassette. Poem by Maralyn Lois Polak, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Dicshtin: String Quartet "Franie". For violin, viola, cello and bass, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Doran, Matt H.: Piano Sonatina No.I, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Dresher, Paul: Guitar Quartet (1975) (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Elliot, Dorothy Gail: Zounds!. A sequential program of creative activites, 1976; 16 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Includes 2 compact audio cassettes.
      RESTRICTED ACCESS: Use of audio material requires the production of listening copies.
    - Fletcher, Grant: Adam. Song for tenor and bass. Text by Nicholas Biel, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Fletcher, Grant: At the Cry of the First Bird, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Fletcher, Grant: By the Waters of Babylon. Psalm 137. SSA choir, soprano solo and piano, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Fletcher, Grant: Caprice A. For cello and piano, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Fletcher, Grant: The Dark Hills. Words by E.A. Robinson., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Fletcher, Grant: Noel, A, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Fletcher, Grant: Rise Up, My Love, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Fletcher, Grant: Pro- Vide. Words by Robert Frost, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Fletcher, Grant: Searching for Lambs, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Fletcher, Grant: Sonata For Viola Alone (IV), undated (Box 3, Folder 2)